Women's Music Archives Collection
Sophia Smith Collection
Women's Music Archives collection
1972-2005
MS 552
79 boxes (circa 75 linear feet)
Sophia Smith Collection Smith College Northampton, MA
The Women's Music Archives Collection consists of bibliographies, biographical sketches, clippings, correspondence, flyers, newsletters, photographs, posters, publicity materials, songbooks, sound recordings, videotapes, and memorabilia. The bulk of the collection dates from 1975 to 1995 and consists of live and studio-produced recordings by women musicians and of women's music festivals, retreats, and conferences. There is also a significant amount of papers documenting the work of individual women musicians, women's music groups and choruses; and the production, distribution, concert booking, and publicity infrastructure for women's music recordings, concerts, festivals, and retreats. Included are extensive records of the North East Women's Music Retreat, a 1980s-90s regional festival, and a substantial set of files from Olivia Records, 1973-94.
During a summer 1975 visit to Maine, friends introduced Lucia "Kim" Kimber and Kathy Lewis to recordings made by Meg Christian, Alix Dobkin, and The Deadly Nightshade. "We were instantly hooked," wrote Kimber in 1985. Two months later, Kimber and Lewis attended the First Boston Women's Music Festival with a small tape deck on which they recorded the two-day long festival held at Harvard University. "That was a mind boggling experience, not only for the music, but it was the first time that I had ever been in an auditorium with 500 women in one spot…. It was the first time that we ever heard music that was aimed particularly at women's issues, and it was composed by women and performed by women." (Lucia Kimber oral history with Amanda Izzo, 2009) Enthralled with the experience, Kimber and Lewis began attending and recording (with the artists' permission) every women's music concert they could get to. They also began collecting studio recordings, books, catalogs, clippings, flyers, posters, programs, memorabilia, newsletters, and other materials related to women's music, including information on artists, production companies, festivals, and the women's music and comedy concert circuit.
Lewis and Kimber first met Ruth Dworin at the 4th National Women's Music Festival in Champaign-Urbana in 1977. Dworin was also making recordings of festival concerts and owned a women's music production company in Toronto called Womanly Way Productions. After meeting at several more events, the three women decided to establish a formal entity to collect and preserve women's music materials. In the fall of 1978 they created the Women's Music Archives as a non-profit organization based at Kimber's home in Fairfield, Connecticut.
According to the WMA's 1980 Catalog, "The primary function of the Women's Music Archives is to collect and preserve, for herstorical listening and research purposes, all types of materials related to women's music." The bulk of the collection focused on "woman-identified, woman-made music, primarily, though not exclusively feminist and lesbian in orientation" that "evolved as a definite entity" beginning in the early 1970s. As the collection grew, Kimber, Lewis, and Dworin added earlier recordings by women "that spoke to the issues which were of vital concern and interest to women." Their Archives was conceived as a means to preserve part of the flourishing and self-affirming lesbian-feminist culture of the day.
In a 1980 article about the Archives for Sojourner, Kimber wrote:
Women derive strength and comfort from many various sources such as feminist literature, women's support groups, communal living situations, and women's art forms such as painting, sculpture, photography, and music…. It is certain…that women's music provides a kind of strength, support and inspiration which is found nowhere else and most certainly is not found in popular music which bombards us constantly over the airways today.
In addition to the Women's Music Archives, Kimber also participated in the "scene" through deep involvement in the North East Women's Musical Retreat (NEWMR), an organization which produced regional outdoor music festivals on Labor Day weekend from 1981 to 2000.
Eager for the Archives to be preserved beyond the lives of its founders, the WMA Directors decided to place it in the Sophia Smith Collection in 2004.
The Women's Music Archives consists of circa 75 linear feet of materials collected and recorded in order to document "woman-identified, woman-made music, primarily, though not exclusively feminist and lesbian in orientation" that "evolved as a definite entity" from the early 1970s. Materials include bibliographies, biographical sketches, clippings, correspondence, flyers, newsletters, photographs, posters, publicity materials, songbooks, sound recordings, videotapes, and memorabilia.
The bulk of the collection dates from 1975 to 1995 and consists of live and studio-produced sound recordings by women musicians and of women's music festivals, retreats, and conferences. The collection also contains significant paper files documenting the work of individual women musicians; women's music groups and choruses; and the production, distribution, concert booking, and publicity infrastructure for women's music recordings, concerts, festivals, and retreats.
Major topics found throughout these files include the women's music movement, women in music more broadly, and differences and diversity within the feminist and lesbian-feminist movement since the 1970s. Though the impetus for founding the collection was "women's music" as it evolved in the early 1970s, there is also material on women in mainstream popular, classical, folk, jazz, blues, punk, and riot grrrl music, as well as stand-up comedy.
The Festivals, Retreats, and Conferences Series documents the thriving women's music, art, theater, and stand-up comedy "scene" (1974-2000), through advertising, newspaper clippings, and packets given out at the festivals. Also included are correspondence with festival organizers, credentials, and release forms for recording live performances for the Women's Music Archives. Especially extensive files on the North East Women's Music Retreat, a 1980s-90s regional festival for which Kim Kimber was a coordinator, reveal the dedication required to plan and produce these complex events. Through the minutes, memoranda, and correspondence, one can also see the ongoing debates and discord surrounding issues such as meaningful inclusion of disabled women, mothers, and women of color; and how to preserve women-only space -- i.e. policies which dictate who can be on the land during the retreat, ranging from male grounds keepers and other personnel to mothers of boy children. The audiovisual materials include extensive live recordings of festivals, concerts, and retreats.
The Artists Series contains press packages, clippings, and photographs. They document well-known artists such as Margie Adam, Meg Christian, Holly Near, Teresa Trull, and Cris Williamson, as well as numerous lesser-known artists. Most of the minor artists' files mainly consist of applications submitted to the North East Women's Music Retreat and accompanying promotional material. There are many stand-up comedians in these files as well.
The Organizations Series contains correspondence, fliers, brochures, and catalogs produced by business organizations and production companies, as well as other non-profit groups focused on women's music. Included is a substantial set of files from Olivia Records composed of correspondence from artists looking to record with Olivia, promotional materials from 1973 through 1994, information for distributors, and clippings, among other items. Of particular interest are the newsletters and correspondence regarding Sandy Stone, a transwoman who worked for Olivia, and some materials regarding Olivia's 1979 change in organizational structure. Other companies with more substantial files include Redwood Records, Goldenrod, Horizon, and Ladyslipper.
The Audiovisual Material Series primarily consists of compact discs, audiocassettes, and LPs. Many of these are live concert and festival recordings, a portion of which have been reformatted to compact disc and are available for research. Please contact the Sophia Smith Collection for more information.
The Reference Materials Series includes bibliographies and research guides, special issues of newsletters and periodicals, pamphlets, directories, and transcripts of interviews with Meg Christian, Holly Near, Susan Freundlich, Margie Adam, Rosemary Schonfeld, and Janna Runnals.
This collection is organized into nine series:
HISTORICAL MATERIALS
ARTIST FILES
FESTIVALS, RETREATS, AND CONFERENCES
ORGANIZATIONS
AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS
SONGBOOKS AND SCORES
REFERENCE MATERIALS
ARTIFACTS AND MEMORABILIA
OVERSIZE MATERIALS
With the exception of the audiovisual items, the materials are open to research according to the regulations of the Sophia Smith Collection without any additional restrictions.
Original live recordings are closed to research. In some cases, in-house use copies have been made. Researchers interested in access to live recordings for which there is no use copy should contact the Sophia Smith Collection to discuss options. With the exception of reformatting for in-house research use, permission from all artists is required before any live tape recordings may be duplicated.
Commercially produced recordings are available for in-house research use provided the Sophia Smith Collection has the equipment necessary to play them. Due to copyright restraints, commercially available recordings may not be reproduced. Many of these materials are available for purchase or download via the Worldwide Web.
Lucia B. "Kim" Kimber donated the Women's Music Archives Collection to the Sophia Smith Collection in 2004.
Feminist music -- Performances; Feminist spirituality -- United States -- History -- Sources; Lesbian feminism -- United States -- History -- Sources; Lesbian musicians; Lesbians -- Songs and music; Music -- Collectors and collecting; Musicians -- United States -- Biography -- Sources; Singers -- United States -- Biography -- Sources; Women composers -- United States -- Biography -- Sources; Women musicians -- United States -- Biography -- Sources; Women singers; Women -- Songs and music; Women's music -- History -- Sources; Women's music festivals; Women's music -- Performances; Dworin, Ruth; Kimber, Lucia C.; Lewis, Kathy; Olivia Records, Inc.
Related materials can be found in the Sophia Smith Collection in the papers of Joan E. Biren, Boden Sandstrom, Diana Davies, Kady, Kay Gardner, Ronnie Gilbert, Tinuviel, Katherine Triantafillou; records of the Sister Singers Network and the Kansas City Womyn's Chorus, and the Music Collection. The Sophia Smith Collection's Periodicals Collection contains full runs of many titles with significant women's music and culture content including, Hot Wire-the Journal of Women's Music and Culture, Lesbian Connection, Media Report to Women, and Off Our Backs. The Five College libraries maintain full runs of Sing Out! in paper and electronic form.
Related materials can also be found at the Schlesinger Library in the Holly Near and Alix Dobkin Papers.
- SERIES I. HISTORICAL MATERIALS 1974-2001, undated, 0.25 linear ft.
  This series includes general historical information about the Women's Music Archives, newspaper clippings about the women's music movement, and a 2009 oral history interview with Lucia B. "Kim" Kimber.
- SERIES II. ARTIST FILES 1964-2006, undated, 7.75 linear ft.
  This series contains biographical and publicity files including newspaper and magazine articles, photographs, fliers, concert programs, and press releases, for individual women, groups, choruses, and choirs, circa 1981-96. The files are arranged alphabetically. See SERIES V. AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS for recordings by these artists.
- SERIES III. FESTIVALS, RETREATS, AND CONFERENCES 1974-2004, 3 linear ft.
  In addition to detailed general files and program brochures of the National Women's Music Festival (NWMF) and North East Women's Music Retreat (NEWMR), this section includes newspaper clippings, fliers, brochures, and concert packets from numerous women's music festivals, circa 1976-2001. The bulk of the materials consist of records of NEWMR. See SERIES V. AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS for recordings of festival performances.
- SERIES IV. ORGANIZATIONS 1974-2005, 2 linear ft.
  This series is comprised of correspondence, fliers, brochures, and catalogs of business organizations and production companies, as well as other non-profit groups focused on women's music, circa 1974-2005. The files are arranged alphabetically. Audition tapes submitted to Olivia Records are in SERIES V. AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS.
- SERIES V. AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS 1960s-2000s
  This series is unprocessed and many of the materials must be reformatted before they can be used. Contact the Sophia Smith Collection for more information.
  Audiovisual materials include live concert and festival recordings, commercial sound recordings, commercial video recordings, tapes of NEWMR planning meetings, audition tapes submitted to Olivia Records and to NEWMR, and a few tapes of the radio program "Face the Music." The materials are in various formats including reel-to-reel audiotape, audiocassette, LP, 45 rpm, CD, videocassette, and DVD.
- SERIES VI. SONGBOOKS AND SCORES circa 1970s-1990s
  This series is unprocessed. Contact the Sophia Smith Collection for more information.
  This series contains songbooks, song sheets, and scores by women musicians or groups, circa 1970s-90s
- SERIES VII. REFERENCE MATERIALS
  Reference files include women's music publications, periodicals,and directories.
- SERIES VIII. ARTIFACTS AND MEMORABILIA
  This series contains a sampling of memorabilia from women's music concerts and festivals, such as t-shirts, hats, stickers, buttons, and other artifacts.
- SERIES IX. OVERSIZE MATERIALS
- SERIES I. HISTORICAL MATERIALS
  - General 1980-85 (Box 1)
  - Oral history interview with Lucia "Kim" Kimber by Amanda Izzo24 Feb 2009 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence
    - General 1979-90, undated (Box 1)
    - Re: Olivia audition tapes 1983 (Box 1)
  - Clippings
    - General 1974-2001, undated (Box 1)
    - Jazz and blues 1979-2003 (Box 1)
    - Punk and riot grrrl 1995-2004 (Box 1)
- SERIES II. ARTIST FILES
  - 320 East Ripaundated (Box 1)
  - 4D YKES 2002, undated (Box 1)
  - A (Box 1)
  - Abod, Susan 1982-95, undated (Box 1)
  - Abrams, Ann 1985-91, undated (Box 1)
  - Absalom, Riaundated (Box 1)
  - Adam, Margie 1982-2005, undated (Box 1)
  - Alder, D.J. (Deb) 1982-84, undated (Box 1)
  - Alder, Lindsay 1985, undated (Box 1)
  - Alexander and Noelle 1981-84, undated (Box 1)
  - Alive! 1981-83, undated (Box 1)
  - Allen, Lillian 1983-88, undated (Box 1)
  - Allen, Linda 1983-89, undated (Box 1)
  - Allison, Sparkie 1981-87, undated (Box 1)
  - Alpert, Rache 1987-89, undated (Box 1)
  - Altazor 1988-92, undated (Box 1)
  - Amethyst 1987-88, undated (Box 1)
  - Amethyst County 1989, undated (Box 1)
  - Anderson, Jamie 1989-2001, undated (Box 1)
  - Anderson, Lauraundated (Box 1)
  - Anna Crusis Choir 1981-1989, undated (Box 1)
  - Another Octave/Conn Women's Chorus 1990-2006 (Box 1)
  - Ars Pro Feminaundated (Box 1)
  - Atabex 1984-1989, undated (Box 1)
  - Avedis, Sirani 1980, undated (Box 1)
  - Avery, Gwen 1979, undated (Box 1)
  - B (Box 1)
  - Baba Yagaundated (Box 1)
  - Bachelorettes 1981, undated (Box 1)
  - Bagby, Rachel 1989, undated (Box 1)
  - Bagwell and Winslow 1987, undated (Box 1)
  - Baker, Brenda 1987-91, undated (Box 1)
  - Bales, Ginny 1979-82, undated (Box 1)
  - Barber, Kitty 1987, undated (Box 1)
  - Barrett, Ruth 1991, undated (Box 1)
  - Barton, Barb 1990-97, undated (Box 1)
  - Barton, Carrie 1981, 1985, undated (Box 1)
  - Bascombe, Lorretta (and Spirit) 1984-85, undated (Box 1)
  - Be Be K'Roche 1976-77, 1988 (Box 1)
  - Ben, Lisa 1982-2002, undated (Box 1)
  - Berezan, Jennifer 1988-92 (Box 1)
  - Berkeley Women's Music Collective 1979, undated (Box 1)
  - Berkson, Laura 1988-91, undated (Box 1)
  - Birtha, Becky 1989, undated (Box 1)
  - Bishop, Heather 1987-89, undated (Box 1)
  - Bitch and Animal 1999-2002 (Box 1)
  - Blazing Saxes 1982-83, undated (Box 2)
  - Bond, Narissa 1995-97, undated (Box 2)
  - Bonnet, Alicia Leonilda "Bubbles" 1988, undated (Box 2)
  - Booth, Pat 1980-86, undated (Box 2)
  - Bozena, Carol 1985-86, undated (Box 2)
  - Bottomley, Judith and Jennifer (Twin Tide)undated (Box 2)
  - Bougainvillea 1981-85, undated (Box 2)
  - Bowly, Laura 1997, undated (Box 2)
  - Boyd, Marcie 1982-88, undated (Box 2)
  - Boyle, Lindaundated (Box 2)
  - Byham, Sue Marra 1995 (Box 2)
  - Brandy, Carolynundated (Box 2)
  - Bratty, Beverly 1987-89 (Box 2)
  - Bread and Roses 1984-85, undated (Box 2)
  - Brico, Antoniaundated (Box 2)
  - Brodsky, Marla B.B. 1983-89, undated (Box 2)
  - Brooks, Nancy 1982, 2002, undated (Box 2)
  - Burris, Carole Anne 1987-90 (Box 2)
  - C (Box 2)
  - Callahan, Slique 1985-90, undated (Box 2)
  - Campbell, Sarah Elizabeth 1991-92, undated (Box 2)
  - Candace & Camille 1988-91, undated (Box 2)
  - Cantilena Wind Quartet 1984, undated (Box 2)
  - Caputi, Anne 1981-84 (Box 2)
  - Carmitchell, Bobbi 1987, undated (Box 2)
  - Carpenter, Beverly 1981-88, undated (Box 2)
  - Carter, Betty 1981, 1986 (Box 2)
  - Carter, Judy 1992-93, undated (Box 2)
  - Casselberry and Dupree 1984-96, undated (Box 2)
  - Cassella, Maggieundated (Box 2)
  - Cazden, Joanna 1984, 1994, undated (Box 2)
  - Chamberlain, Anne 1991 (Box 2)
  - Chandler, Teresa 1989-90, undated (Box 2)
  - Chapman, Tracy 1985-89, undated (Box 2)
  - Cheney, Joyce 1985, undated (Box 2)
  - Cherish the Ladies 1985-87, undated (Box 2)
  - Cherry Cokes, The undated (Box 2)
  - Chevere 1985, undated (Box 2)
  - Chicago Women's Liberation Rock Band 2002 (Box 2)
  - Christian, Meg 1977-95, undated (Box 2)
  - Clark, Barbara 1979 (Box 2)
  - Clemmens, Ginni 1980, 1998, undated (Box 2)
  - Clinton, Kate 1981-2001, undated (Box 2)
  - Collier, Linda 1989, undated (Box 2)
  - Collins, Mitzieundated (Box 2)
  - Concerted Effortundated (Box 2)
  - Conn, Marjorie 1999, undated (Box 2)
  - Cook, Cathy 1984, undated (Box 2)
  - Cooney, Christine 1985, undated (Box 2)
  - Cotton, Elizabeth 1987, undated (Box 2)
  - Cotto, Rayda 1983, undated (Box 2)
  - Cowboy Girl 1992-95 (Box 2)
  - Crowsfeet Dance Collective 1985-89, undated (Box 2)
  - CT and April 1982, undated (Box 2)
  - Cullum, Linda 1983-88, undated (Box 2)
  - Culver, Casse 1972-82, undated (Box 2)
  - Curtis, Catie 1989-96, undated (Box 2)
  - Curtis, Pamela 1984-85, undated (Box 2)
  - Cygnus 1990, undated (Box 2)
  - Cytron, Sara 1988-93, undated (Box 2)
  - D (Box 2)
  - D'Amato, Catherine 1980-86, undated (Box 2)
  - Dance Brigade 1986-89, undated (Box 2)
  - Dashu, Max 1989 (Box 2)
  - Davidson, Dianne 1987-94 (Box 2)
  - Davies, Diana 1982, undated (Box 2)
  - Davis, Hunter 1983-89, undated (Box 2)
  - Day, Nancy 1984, 1987, undated (Box 2)
  - D.C. Area Feminist Chorus (Box 2)
  - Dee, Cristi 1989-90, undated (Box 2)
  - Del Ray and the Blues Gators 1990, undated (Box 2)
  - DeLaria, Lea 1990-93, undated (Box 2)
  - Dembska, Anna 1984, undated (Box 2)
  - Demi/Monde 1986-87, undated (Box 2)
  - Denver Women's Chorus 1988-97 (Box 2)
  - Destiny 1990-97, undated (Box 3)
  - Deuce 1980-87, undated (Box 3)
  - Devon, Cruz 1983, undated (Box 3)
  - Dickens, Hazel 1981 (Box 3)
  - Different Touch 1989, undated (Box 3)
  - Difranco, Ani 1994-98 (Box 3)
  - Di Micele, Alice 1988-1992, undated (Box 3)
  - Dinerman, Annie 1973-99 (Box 3)
  - disappear fear 1988-2005 (Box 3)
  - Dixon, Fostina 1984-85, undated (Box 3)
  - Dobkin, Alix 1979-2005, undated (Box 3)
  - Dos Fallopia 1991, undated (Box 3)
  - Drach, Tracy 1991-93, undated (Box 3)
  - Duffus, Anne 1985, undated (Box 3)
  - Dufresne, Dusti 1992, undated (Box 3)
  - Dunn, Barb 1982-83, undated (Box 3)
  - [The Fabulous] Dyketones 1981-84, undated (Box 3)
  - E (Box 3)
  - Edell, Therese 1978-91, undated (Box 3)
  - Einhorn, Lena 1987, 1992, undated (Box 3)
  - Elliot, [Gwen] GEeundated (Box 3)
  - Ends and Means Committee 1981-82, undated (Box 3)
  - Ester, Barbara 1990, 1993, undated (Box 3)
  - Etheridge, Melissa 1989-95, undated (Box 3)
  - Etzler, Carole 1983-88, undated (Box 3)
  - Exit 154 1989-91, undated (Box 3)
  - F (Box 3)
  - Farrell, Alison 1979-85, undated (Box 3)
  - Fasteau, Zususan Kali 1974-89, undated (Box 3)
  - Feld, Janet 1988-89, undated (Box 3)
  - Feldheim, Michele 1984, undated (Box 3)
  - Feldman, Maxine 1974-95, undated (Box 3)
  - Ferguson, Robin 1985-89, undated (Box 3)
  - Ferron 1981-96, undated (Box 3)
  - Field, Robin 1989, undated (Box 3)
  - Fier, Debbie 1980-89, undated (Box 3)
  - Fink and Marxer 1982-89 (Box 3)
  - Fink, Sue 1978-96, undated (Box 3)
  - First Strike Theater Co.undated (Box 3)
  - Fjell, Judy 1981-89 (Box 3)
  - Flower, Robin 1978-91, undated (Box 3)
  - Focal Point 1987-88, undated (Box 3)
  - Ford, Eileen 1984, undated (Box 3)
  - Fóta, Jamie 1993-97, undated (Box 3)
  - Fox, Mimi 1981, undated (Box 3)
  - Free, Jill 1981, undated (Box 3)
  - Free River 1985, undated (Box 3)
  - Freeway Fusion 1987, undated (Box 3)
  - Freundlich, Susan 1979-85, undated (Box 3)
  - Friedman, Judi 1984-91, undated (Box 3)
  - Friesen, Cate 1988-90, undated (Box 3)
  - Fure, Tret 1985-2002, undated (Box 3)
  - G (Box 3)
  - Gal (Janice Perry) 1981-93, undated (Box 3)
  - Galey and Gonzales 1989 (Box 3)
  - Gardner, Kay 1974-2002, undated (Box 3)
  - Garthwaite, Terry 1979-82, undated (Box 4)
  - Gates, Purly 1982-93, undated (Box 4)
  - Gemini, Mary 1983-89, undated (Box 4)
  - Genfan, Vicki 1986, undated (Box 4)
  - Gerendasy, Carrie 1985-88, undated (Box 4)
  - German, Miriam 1989, undated (Box 4)
  - Gilbert, Ronnie 1981-88, undated (Box 4)
  - The Girlillas 1982-90, undated (Box 4)
  - Girls in the Nose 1988-96, undated (Box 4)
  - Glastonbury 1988-89, undated (Box 4)
  - Glenn-Copeland, Beverlyundated (Box 4)
  - Goddess Gospel 1989-91, undated (Box 4)
  - Goldspinner (Wattles, J.) 1984, undated (Box 4)
  - Gomez, Marga 1981-98, undated (Box 4)
  - Good for a Girl 1988, undated (Box 4)
  - Goodman, Eve 1989, undated (Box 4)
  - Gorman-Jacobs, Judy 1985, undated (Box 4)
  - Gowdey, Rosi 1984-85, undated (Box 4)
  - Grace and Goddess Unlimited 1985-86, undated (Box 4)
  - Graetz, Susan 1981-85, undated (Box 4)
  - Grant, Monica 1988-92, undated (Box 4)
  - Gray, Lisa 1991, undated (Box 4)
  - Gribi, Gerri 1984-85, undated (Box 4)
  - The Guest Stars 1984, undated (Box 4)
  - Gygax, Lisa Lynn 1988, undated (Box 4)
  - Gyra 1992, undated (Box 4)
  - H (Box 4)
  - Hamilton, Karen 1985 (Box 4)
  - Handleman, Randieundated (Box 4)
  - Haney, Lynn 1987, undated (Box 4)
  - Hannan, Kathleen 1990-92, undated (Box 4)
  - Haresuite 1985, undated (Box 4)
  - Harris, Hillary 1986-87, undated (Box 4)
  - Harrison, Joy Edenundated (Box 4)
  - Hawkins and DeLear 1984-86, undated (Box 4)
  - The Heretics 1989-91, undated (Box 4)
  - The Heroines 1987-90, undated (Box 4)
  - Herrick, Susan 1986-96, undated (Box 4)
  - Higbie, Barbara 1980-85, undated (Box 4)
  - Hill, Nancy 1986-90, undated (Box 4)
  - Hines, Ellen 1991, undated (Box 4)
  - Hirsch, Dorothy 1989-97, undated (Box 4)
  - Hirschhorn, Linda 1982-90, undated (Box 4)
  - Hoffman, Nan 1983-85, undated (Box 4)
  - The Holy War 1983-85, undated (Box 4)
  - Hollander, Anita 1981-82, undated (Box 4)
  - Holtz, Teddy and Leaf Miller 1983, undated (Box 4)
  - Homi, Julie 1979-92, undated (Box 4)
  - Hooke, Helen 1981-99 (Box 4)
  - Humphries, Pat 1987-90, undated (Box 4)
  - Hunt, Janis 1989-90, undated (Box 4)
  - I (Box 4)
  - Ian, Janis 1980-2006 (Box 4)
  - Iris 1987-88, undated (Box 4)
  - Ishantova, Davida 1981-82, undated (Box 4)